Ripped up statements stacked on my floor Calculators frat since 94 Boss said save but I need it more Broken system ticking down the door Empty pockets and they still want more Panic spurling every market score
Thriving deep at politicians' lore.
Crashing dreams that I can't ignore.
Teeping deep in my 401k hole.
Numb the slip in my future dead soul.
Inflation biting right through my soul.
Can I retire, still feel it won't?
Oh, oh, down we go.
Sheriff slammed my savings to the floor.
Puppets laugh as my balance reads poor.
Bunch of dreams, yeah, they're shown the door.
Spending less just isn't punk anymore.
We planned, we saved, we barely got by.
Now they tax and blame a foreign supply.
Chasing dollars that just flutter and die.
But we're too broke to even ask why.
Diving deep in my 401k hole.
Numbers slip and my guitar gets sold.
In flesh, whining might fill my soul.
Did I retire, still feeling whole?
Oh, oh, damn me, girl.